ringid.com 2015-09-24

# ringID | Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy  
(EFFECTIVE AS OF JULY 25, 2015)

Ring Incorporated ("ringID" or "we" or "us" or "our" or other similar pronouns) understands that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of ringID when you access and use the Website (ringID.com) and when you use your Devices to access and use the Service, how we receive, collect and use information in connection with our website located at ringID.com and the ringID software ("ringID App"), and other products and services provided on the ringID.com website (all of the foregoing, collectively, the "Service"). 

At ringID we understand the importance of your disclosed information and hence have designed a privacy policy which we believe will best suite your data protection concerns in concurrence with our operational process. 

ringID is committed to value and secure the privacy of any private and confidential data that you deliver to us while using our service. At ringID, we obtain additional watchful measures to ensure that all the data we hold in our data center related to you is accurate, precise and secured. Valuable Information is stored on our servers and sheltered by safe networks which are subject to limited access to a few approved employees and personnel. However, it is to be noted that, any system of communication over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, cannot be considered as fully secured. 

It is probable that you have downloaded the ringID application from our site or any other site. Furthermore, there are possibilities that our site may contain links which will make you attend some other website and leave our site. It is to be noted that websites which are linked to or from our site do not fall under the control of ringID and they most likely will have a privacy policy which will be different than ours. Our policies apply exclusively to personal information that is collected on the site or by the means of your use of our service and/or your experience with ringID. We strongly suggest that you should be careful while you are providing any personal information online. For any other website we adhere to no responsibility or liability of any kind. 

In this section, we look forward to clarify the facts regarding how ringID collects, stores and uses your data and the security measures taken to protect it. 

By visiting this Site or using the Service, you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Policy, as such Policy may be amended from time to time. Each time you visit the Site or use the Service, you agree and expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of the information that you provide as described in this Policy. 

To clarify about the terminology we are using, when we use the phrase "Personal Information" in this Policy, we mean information about you that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, e-mail address, billing information, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with this personal information. When we use the phrase "Anonymous Information" in this Policy, we mean information that is not personally identifiable, or linked to your Personal Information such as aggregated information, general demographic information and IP addresses. Anonymous Information does not necessarily enable identification of individual persons. 

IF YOU ARE A USER ACCESSING THE SITE OR SERVICE FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, ASIA, OR ANY OTHER REGION WITH LAWS OR REGULATIONS GOVERNING PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE THAT DIFFER FROM CANADA OR UNITED STATES LAWS, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE AND SERVICE, WHICH ARE GOVERNED BY UNITED STATES LAW, THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND OUR END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT, YOU MAY BE TRANSMITTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO COUNTRIES (INCLUDING CANADA AND THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION IN YOUR COUNTRY AND YOU HEREBY CONSENT TO SUCH TRANSMISSION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. 

### ringID App 

When you install the ringID App, you will be asked to provide us with your phone number and name and you will allow us access to your mobile device's address book. 

A copy of the phone numbers and names in your address book (but not emails, notes or any other Personal Information in your address book) will be stored on our servers and will only be used to: 

(a) inform you when your contacts turn active on ringID,   
(b) specify which of your contacts is already a ringID user,   
(c) precisely show the name of every contact as it is in your address book when you receive a call.  
(d) sync your contacts with ringID running on any other platform. 

If you delete your address book which contains names and phones, from our servers, it will be deleted permanently straightaway. This is because the copy of your address book is stored on a live database which does not have a "historical backup". 

Your phone number, which will be verified via a passcode that will be sent to you, will be used for identification purposes as your ringID user ID. 

As other ringID users may add your ringID number to their address book and see that you registered to ringID, we do not consider the fact that your ringID number exists on ringID as private information. 

ringID also maintains a Call Detail Record (CDR - see http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Call_detail_record) for each message and call that goes through the system. These are industry standard records used by all phone companies. We maintain this information in order to better understand network behavior and trends (numbers of messages and calls made by users, typical destinations, call lengths, network type, etc.), detect potential outages and technical issues (this helps us notice things like a drop in call volume in a certain geography, a shift in call length, a change in typical networks, etc.) and for public safety reasons. All log analysis is done in an anonymous, aggregate, non-personally identifiable manner. We may look into a specific Call Detail Record in response to a customer support request. We maintain CDRs for a period of no more than 30 months. 

Audio calls by users are transmitted either directly from user to user or, if direct transmission is not possible (due to, for example, firewalls), ringID servers are used to transmit the call. In the latter scenario, the information transmitted is stored briefly in volatile memory (RAM) solely to enable the transmission of the call to the other user. WE DO NOT RECORD ANY PART OF YOUR CALL. 

It might be necessary for ringID to interrelate with your phone's SMS inbox or call history for the lone purpose of service activation, placing incoming messages in your inbox, reading the contents of the activation SMS sent to you by ringID. WE WILL NOT ACCESS THE CONTENTS OF ANY OTHER SMS.

### Information We Receive About You 

We receive a number of different types of information about you, including: 

Your Information 

Your information is the information that's required when you sign up for the site, as well as the information you choose to share. 

Registration information: 

When you sign up for ringID, you are required to provide information such as your name, email address, birthday, gender and your telephone number. Information you choose to share:   
Your information also includes the information you choose to share on ringID, such as when you post a status update, upload a photo, or comment on a friend's story. 

It also includes the information you choose to share when you communicate with us, such as when you contact us using an email address, or when you take an action, such as when you add a friend, like a Circle or a Group, add a place to your posts, use our contact importers or share other updates and uploads. 

Your name, profile pictures, cover photos, gender, networks, username and User ID are treated just like information you choose to make public. 

Your birthday allows us to do things like show you age-appropriate content. 

### Name and Photo 

If you provide your name and/or photo it will be visible to other ringID users as long as: 

Such users have your ringID number, or 

You participate in the same Group with the users 

### Location Information 

Location related information may be passed out by your device which might be used by ringID to provide the specific service. However, you can choose their location information not to be shared. 

ringID allows you to attach your location information to messages you send to other users or send a specific location message. If you choose to share your location with a specific user or group of users, your location will be retrieved from your device and sent to ringID. ringID will only use this location for this particular purpose and delete it from its servers once the message is delivered. For the avoidance of doubt, ringID will not share your location information and will not use it for any purpose except the one specifically requested by you. 

### Use of Other User Information 

In order to provide a more vibrant social experience, you might be asked to provide additional information which might include full name, display names, photos, messages, birth date etc. It is also possible for other users to visit and view profiles and other information which might include text, images, and videos etc. which have been submitted by the users themselves in order to share with others. Even though you might decide not to submit such information which is permissible, however, this might result in disabling you to avail all or parts of the features of ringID. 

### Use of Logs 

While using ringID, your log related information such as IP address, browser kind, browser name, browser language etc. will be collected and stored as an automatic process. The obtained information can be used by ringID to enhance the service standards offered and also take measures against harmful practices which create disturbance within regular service process. 

### Cookies, Clear GIFs and Other Automatically Collected Data 

To be in a position to offer you a better customer experience. We use technologies like cookies, pixels, and local storage (like on your browser or device, which is similar to a cookie but holds more information) to provide and understand a range of products and services. We use cookies to provide and improve our services and store information about your preferences. By using our service, you agree to this. 

We use these technologies to do things like:

make ringID easier or faster to use; 

enable features and store information about you (including on your device or in your browser cache) and your use of ringID; 

monitor and understand the use of our products and services; and, 

secure you, others and the ringID application. 

Please read our cookie policy below to learn more about the information we store and how it can be used. 

### Other Information We Receive About You 

We also receive other types of information about you: 

We receive data about you whenever you use or are running ringID, such as when you look at another person's timeline, send or receive a message, search for a friend or a Circle, click on, view or otherwise interact with things, using the ringID app. 

When you post things like photos or videos on ringID, we may receive additional related data (or metadata), such as the time, date, and place you took the photo or video. 

We receive your IP address and other related information you use to install ringID apps or to access ringID, including when multiple users log in from the same device. This may include network and communication information, such as your IP address or mobile phone number, and other information about things like your internet service, operating system, location, the type (including identifiers) of the device or browser you use, or the pages you visit. For example, we may get your GPS or other location information so we can tell you if any of your friends are nearby, or we could request device information to improve how our apps work on your device. 

We receive data whenever you visit a game, application, or website that uses ringID Platform or visit a site with a ringID feature (such as a social plugin), sometimes through cookies. This may include the date and time you visit the site; the web address, or URL, you're on; technical information about the IP address, browser and the operating system you use; and, if you are logged in to ringID, your User ID. 

We also put together data from the information we already have about you, your friends, and others, so we can offer and suggest a variety of services and features. For example, we may make friend suggestions, pick stories for your newsfeed, or suggest people to tag in photos. We may put together your current city with GPS and other location information we have about you to, for example, tell you and your friends about people or events nearby, or offer deals to you in which you might be interested. We may also put together data about you to serve you ads or other content that might be more relevant to you.

When we get your GPS location, we put it together with other location information we have about you (like your current city). But we only keep it until it is no longer useful to provide you services, like keeping your last GPS coordinates to send you relevant notifications. 

### Third-Party Sites and Privacy Practices 

You may arrive at our Site and/or download the ringID App from another website. In addition, our Site may contain links that will let you leave our Site and access another website. Websites linked to or from our Site are not under the control of ringID and it is possible that these websites have a different privacy policy. Our Policy applies solely to Personal Information that is acquired on the Site or through your use of our Service, and/or your relationship with ringID. We urge you to be careful when you enter any Personal Information online. We accept no responsibility or liability for these other websites. 

### Public Information 

When we use the phrase "public information", we mean the information you choose to make public, as well as information that is always publicly available.

### Information You Choose to Make Public

Choosing to make your information public is exactly what it sounds like: anyone, including people not associated with ringID, will also be able to see it. 

Choosing to make your information public also means that this information: 

can be associated with you (i.e., your name, profile pictures, cover photos, timeline, User ID, username, etc.) even off ringID; 

can show up when someone does a search on ringID or on a public search engine; 

will be accessible to the ringID-integrated games, applications, and websites you and your friends use; and 

Sometimes you will not be able to select an audience when you post something. This is because some types of stories are always public stories. As a general rule, you should assume that if you do not see a sharing icon, the information will be publicly available.

When others share information about you, they can also choose to make it public. 

### Information that is Always Publicly Available 

The types of information listed below are always publicly available, and they are treated just like information you decided to make public: 

Name:

o This helps your friends and family to find you. 

Profile Pictures and Cover Photos: 

o These help your friends and family to recognize you. If you are uncomfortable in making any of these photos public, you can always delete them. Unless you delete them, when you add a new profile picture or cover photo, the previous photo will remain public in your profile picture or cover photo album. 

Networks: 

o This helps you to see with whom you will be sharing information before you choose your audience. If you are uncomfortable making your network public, you can leave the network. 

Gender: 

o This allows us to refer to you properly. 

Username and User ID: 

o These allow you to give out a custom link to your timeline or Page, receive email at your ringID email address, and help make ringID Platform possible. 

## 2\. Sharing and Disclosure of Information Back to top

We do not rent, sell, or share any information about our users with any third-parties, except as specifically described herein. We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe such action is necessary to: 

(a) comply with the law, or legal process served on us; 

(b) protect and defend our rights or property (including the enforcement of our agreements); or 

(c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of our Service or members of the public. 

In order to register with ringID, you will have to provide first name, last name, gender, cell phone number, username and password. You also need to agree with the terms and conditions of ringID to complete the registration process. ringID will store user data such as messages, call reports etc. 

ringID will use your cell phone number to search other ringID users in the contact list and make friend suggestions. Moreover, acquisition of your cell phone number also verifies the identity of the user and helps to avoid any unapproved use of ringID. 

Your phone book in your cell phone will be used to search other ringID users in your contact list and make friend suggestions. 

The aforementioned information of the user will be kept such that it will be visible to other users. It is up to the sole consent of the user whether or not to submit the required information. However, non-submission of information might result in the prevention of using any of the ringID features or parts of it. If a user account is deleted, such user information will be deleted as per the company policies. 

In order to provide you with ringID products you have requested, ringID may sometimes, if necessary, share your Personal Information (excluding your address book and related information) and traffic data with trusted partner service providers and/or agents, for example: payment processors or other providers of payment and analytical services, customer support, or hosting services. ringID will always require these third parties to take appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect your personal data and traffic data and to observe the relevant legislation. ringID will never share your address book information with any third party, except as may be required by law .

### Third Party Policy 

The following is a description of how we may share your Personal Information with trusted third party partners. Should we add additional partners, we will immediately update this description: 

1\. We may use Push Notification Services to notify you about various events related to the app. If we do, the phone number or the name of the person calling you or sending you a message may be part of the notification. This message is sent to the push notification service provider, for delivery to your device. 

2\. We use third parties to process the payment and/or billing information that you submit on our Site or through the ringID App to facilitate payment transactions. We require that these third parties take the appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect your personal data and traffic data and to comply with relevant laws.

We may disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance that disclosure of information is necessary. 

We may from time to time ask you to provide information about your experiences, which will be used to measure and improve quality. You are at no time under any obligation to provide any of such data. Any and all information which is voluntarily submitted in feedback forms on the Site or any survey that you accept to take part in is used for the purposes of reviewing this feedback and improving the ringID software, products and websites. 

We may contact you to send you messages about faults and service issues. Furthermore, we reserve the right to use email, the ringID software or SMS to notify you of any eventual claims related to your use of our software, websites and/or products, including without limitation claims of violation of third party rights. 

We may send you alerts via the ringID software to notify you when someone has tried to contact you. We may also use the ringID software to keep you up to date with news about our software and products that you have purchased and/or to inform you about other ringID products and related information. 

### How We Use the Information We Receive 

We use the information we receive about you in connection with the services and features we provide to you and other users like your friends, and the developers that build the games, applications, and websites you use. For example, in addition to helping people see and find things that you do and share, we may use the information we receive about you: 

as part of our efforts to keep ringID products, services and integrations safe and secure; 

to protect ringID's or others' rights or property; 

to provide you with location features and services, like telling you and your friends when something is going on nearby; 

to make suggestions to you and other users on ringID, such as: suggesting that your friend to use our contact importer because you found friends using it, suggesting that another user adds you as a friend because the user imported the same email address as you did, or suggesting that your friend tag you in a picture they have uploaded with you in it; and 

for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research and service improvement. 

As you grant us the permission to use your information, it helps us to provide you with better service features and further improve our offerings for the future. While you are allowing us to use the information we receive about you, you always own all of your information. Your trust is important to us, which is why we don't share information we receive about you with others unless we have: 

received your permission; 

given you notice, such as by telling you about it in this policy; or 

removed your name and any other personally identifying information from it. 

Of course, for information that others share about you, they control how it is shared. We store data for as long as it is necessary to provide products and services to you and others, including those described above. Typically, information associated with your account will be kept until your account is deleted. For certain categories of data, we may also tell you about specific data retention practices. 

We may enable access to public information that has been shared through our services. 

We may allow service providers to access information so they can help us provide services. 

### Control Each Time You Post 

Whenever you post content (like a status update, photo or check-in), you can select a specific audience, or even customize your audience. 

It is highly recommended that you always think before you post. Just like anything else you post on the web or send in an email, information you share on ringID can be copied or shared by anyone who can see it. 

Although you choose with whom you share, there may be ways for others to determine information about you. For example, if you hide your birthday so no one can see it on your timeline, but friends post "happy birthday!" on your timeline, people may determine your birthday. 

When you comment on or like someone else's story, or write on their timeline, that person gets to select the audience. For example, if a friend posts a Public story and you comment on it, your comment will be Public. Often, you can see the audience someone selected for their story before you post a comment; however, the person who posted the story may later change their audience. So, if you comment on a story, and the story’s audience changes, the new audience can see your comment.

Sometimes you will not see a sharing icon when you post something (like when you write on a Page's wall or comment on a news article that uses our comments plugin). This is because some types of stories are always public stories. As a general rule, you should assume that if you do not see a sharing icon, the information will be publicly available. 

### Control Over Your Timeline 

Whenever you add things to your timeline you can select a specific audience, or even customize your audience.

When you select an audience for your friend list, you are only controlling who can see the entire list of your friends on your timeline. Your friend list is always available to the games, applications and websites you use, and your friendships may be visible elsewhere (such as on your friends' timelines or in searches). 

Similarly, if you choose to hide your gender, it only hides it on your timeline. This is because we, just like the applications you and your friends use; need to use your gender to refer to you properly on the site. 

When you hide things on your timeline, like posts or connections, it means those things will not appear on your timeline. But, remember, anyone in the audience of those posts or who can see a connection may still see it elsewhere, like on someone else's timeline or in search results. You can also delete your posts or change the audience of content you post. 

People on ringID may be able to see mutual friends, even if they cannot see your entire list of friends. Some things (like your name, profile pictures and cover photos) do not have sharing icons because they are always publicly available. As a general rule, you should assume that if you do not see a sharing icon, the information will be publicly available. 

### Finding You on ringID

To make it easier for your friends to find you, we allow anyone with your contact information (such as email address or telephone number) to find you through the ringID search bar as well as other tools we provide, such as contact importers - even if you have not shared your contact information with them on ringID. 

You can choose who can look up your timeline using the email address or telephone number you added to your timeline through your privacy settings. . But remember that people can still find you or a link to your timeline on ringID through other people and the things they share about you or through other posts, like if you are tagged in a friend's photo or post. 

Your settings do not control whether people can find you or a link to your timeline when they search for content they have permission to see, like a photo or other story in which you've been tagged. 

### Access on Phones and Other Devices 

Once you share information with your friends and others, they may be able to sync it with or access it via their mobile phones and other devices. For example, if you share a photo on ringID, someone viewing that photo could save it using ringID tools or by other methods offered by their device or browser. Similarly, if you share your contact information with someone or invite someone, they may be able to use ringID or third-party applications or devices to sync that information. Or, if one of your friends has a ringID application on one of their devices, your information (such as the things you post or photos you share) may be stored on or accessed by their device. 

You should only share information with people you trust because they will be able to save it or re-share it with others, including when they sync the information to a device. 

### Your Own Feed 

Your own feed is your activity log where you can go to view most of your information on ringID, including things you've hidden from your timeline. You can use this to manage your content. For example, you can do things like delete stories, change the audience of your stories or stop an application from publishing to your timeline on your behalf. 

When you hide something from your timeline, you are not deleting it. This means that the story may be visible elsewhere, like in your friends' News Feed. If you want to delete a story you posted, choose the delete option. 

## 4\. Children's Privacy Back to top

ringID websites and software clients are not intended for or designed to attract anyone under the age of 13 and we do not intentionally or knowingly collect Personal Information on our sites from anyone under the age of 13 (or older in some jurisdictions). We encourage parents to be involved in the online activities of their children to ensure that no information is collected from a child without parental permission.

## 5\. Security Back to top

We take reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although we cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, we have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in place to protect Personal Information. Personal Information is stored on our servers and protected by secured networks to which access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. 

##  6\. Changes to Policy Back to top

From time to time, we may revise this Policy. We reserve the right to update or modify this Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time with or without notice. However, we will not use your Personal Information in a way that is materially different than the uses described in this Policy without giving you an opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. We will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information we collect, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. You agree to review the Policy periodically so that you are aware of any modifications. Your continued usage of the Site indicates your assent to any changes and signifies your agreement to the terms of our Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the Site, the ringID App, or any other Service. 

### Notice of Changes 

If we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you accordingly. If the changes are material, we will provide you additional, prominent notice as appropriate under the circumstances. 

## 7\. Change or Removal of Information Back to top

If you provided your e-mail address to us and wish to update it, you may do so by sending an e-mail to [support@ringID.com](mailto:support@ringid.com)

If you no longer wish to receive e-mail communication from us, such as offers, updates and newsletters, you may opt-out of receiving such communications by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. In addition, you can remove your e-mail address at any time by sending an e-mail with the subject line of UNSUBSCRIBE to [unsubscribe@ringID.com](mailto:unsubscribe@ringid.com)

## 8\. Cookie Policy Back to top

If you have permitted your computer to accept cookies, we may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at the Site. Cookies may be used to analyze the Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. A cookie may enable us to relate your use of our Site to other information about you, including your Personal Information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on our Site. Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Site or certain areas or features of the Site. 

Pixels are small blocks of code on webpages that do things like allowing another server to measure viewing of a webpage and often are used in connection with cookies. We may use "clear GIFs" (aka "Web beacons" or "pixel tags") or similar technologies, in the Site and/or in our communications with you to enable us to evaluate Site usage information about visitors to the Site, target campaigns, upgrade visitor information, and know whether you have visited a Web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a Web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual's viewing or receipt of a Web page or message. A clear gif may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a Web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information. 

Our servers may automatically collect data about your Internet address when you visit the Site. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you are on the Internet. When you request pages from our Site, our servers may log your IP Address and, if applicable, your domain name. Your IP Address is used to help identify you and to gather demographic information about our members and users as a whole, but does not include personally identifiable information. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another web site or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Site; the web site you visit after this Site; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Site or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data logged by our servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Service. Such information may also be used to gather demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. 

We will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of our users. 

Any or all of these activities with regard to Site usage information may be performed on our behalf by our service providers, including, for example, our analytics vendor(s) and our e-mail management partner(s). 

Cookies and things like local storage help make ringID work, like allowing pages to load faster because certain content is stored on your browser or by helping us to authenticate you to deliver personalized content. 

### Access Requests 

You can access and correct most of your personal data stored by ringID by logging into your account and viewing your timeline and activity log. 

### Notifications and Other Messages 

We may send you notifications and other messages using the contact information we have for you. You can control most of the notifications you receive, using controls we provide.

### Invitations 

When you invite a friend to join ringID, we send a message on your behalf using your name, and we may also include names and pictures of other people your friend might know on ringID. 

### Security and Bugs 

We at Ring Inc. are working tirelessly at our best to keep your information secured. We try to keep ringID up, bug-free and safe, but can't make guarantees about any part of our services or products.

### Questions or Disputes 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us by mail at [ring@ringID.com](mailto:ring@ringid.com) Anyone may also contact us through our customer support. 

###  Responding to Legal Requests and Preventing Harm 

We may access, preserve and share your information in response to a legal request (like a search warrant, court order or subpoena) if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so. This may include responding to legal requests from jurisdictions outside of Canada where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law in that jurisdiction, affects users in that jurisdiction, and is consistent with internationally recognized standards. We may also access, preserve and share information when we have a good faith as it is necessary to: detect, prevent and address fraud and other illegal activity; to protect ourselves, you and others, including as part of investigations; or to prevent death or imminent bodily harm. Information we receive about you, including financial transaction data related to purchases made with ringID, may be accessed, processed and retained for an extended period of time when it is the subject of a legal request or obligation, governmental investigation, or investigations concerning possible violations of our terms or policies, or otherwise to prevent harm. We also may retain information from accounts disabled for violations of our terms for at least a year to prevent repeat abuse or other violations of our terms. 

### Help and Support 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us by mail at [ring@ringID.com](mailto:ring@ringid.com)
